Local 1199 Publications 6209 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RN Division News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Clinton Outlines Alternative Plan to Halt Deficit, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 8, 1995.
  - Item 27: As Long Promised, President Vetoess the GOP Budget, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Todd S. Purdum
    Notes: New York Times, December 7, 1995.
  - Item 28: A Health Care Merger Teeters, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: Shift is Sought in Financing for Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 6, 1995.
  - Item 30: President Yielding to GOP, Will Offer Plan Erasing Deficit, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Michael Wines
  - Item 31: White House Documents Reveal Similarities to GOP's Plans for Medicare., 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Making the System Work in Kidney Patients Favor, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Kurt Eichenwald
  - Item 33: A Possible Model: Tying Payments to Overall Health, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: New Priorities: Getting Away From Cutting Corners, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 35: Leaders of AMA Critical of Plan to Alter Medicaid, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 5, 1995.
  - Item 36: Deficit Partnership: The Republicans and Democrats Dug the Budget Hole Over 3 Decades, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 3, 1995.
  - Item 37: Budget Talks Face Hurdle of Hostility, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 1, 1995.
  - Item 38: Skyline News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: 95-23 (1995:Nov. 6)
  - Item 39: Congress Approves Unacceptable Budget Reconciliation Bill, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News v.27:no.46 (1995:Nov. 22)
  - Item 40: House and Senate Debate Final Reconciliation Conference Agreement: Partial Government Shutdown Continues, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News v.27:no.45 (1995:Nov. 17)
  - Item 41: From Buffalo to Broadway, New Yorkers Oppose Medicare/Medicaid Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News v.27:no.43 (1995:Nov. 3)
  - Item 42: Congress Approves Unacceptable Budget Reconciliation Bill, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Continuing Care Connection, v.2:no.24 (1995:Nov. 29)
  - Item 43: Certificate of Need Intake Log, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: December 1, 1995.
  - Item 44: Review Outcome Logs, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 45: The Move: Is Your Town Big Enough for the Both of You?, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, November 20, 1995.
  - Item 46: Currents, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, November 5, 1995.
  - Item 47: Federal Deficit Reduction Proposals fro Medicare and Medicaid, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Medical Benefits
    Notes: Medical Benefits, November 15, 1995.
  - Item 48: A Comparative Study of Medicare and Managed Care Pricing, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 49: Managed-Care Insolvency Grows, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, December 8, 1995
  - Item 50: WellPoint Postpones Closing of HSI merger, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, November 27, 1995
  - Item 51: Healthcare Workers' Raises Dwindling, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 52: Medicaid Managed-Care Plans Face Tough New Rules in M.Y., 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 53: A Budget Debate Not About Dollars, But About Whose Plan Makes Sense, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 54: Pataki Asserts Medicaid Rule Won't Change, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 55: Albany Reviewing Medicaid Quotas in Nursing Homes, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 30, 1995.
  - Item 56: Chiefs' Dispute Threat to Merger of 2 California Health Networks, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 28, 1995.
  - Item 57: White House Sets Budget Priorities, Putting Medicaid and Medicare at Top of List, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Alison Mitchell
    Notes: New York Times, November 25, 1995.
  - Item 58: Budget Cuts Stall Broader Services in Medicare Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 24, 1995.
  - Item 59: Director of State AIDS Institute Says She Is Resigning In Protest Over Pataki Policies, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 23, 1995.
  - Item 60: Giuliani to Curtail AIDS Services, Despite Growing Caseload, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Thomas J. Lueck
    Notes: New York Times, November 21, 1995.
  - Item 61: Foster Care Model Attracts New York, But Only In Part, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Kimberly J. McLaren
    Notes: New York Times, November 20, 1995.
  - Item 62: Hospital Bid With Doctors Seems Likely, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 12, 1995.
  - Item 63: Business May Pay More For Health as Congress Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, November 4, 1995.
  - Item 64: OSHA Makes an Issue of Back Injury; Beverly Wins the First Test Case, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: American Journal of Nursing, December, 1995.
  - Item 65: Hospital Execs Navigate Troubled Waters, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 66: Skyline News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: 95-26 (1995:Dec. 18)
  - Item 67: Skyline News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: 95-25 (1995:Dec. 4)
  - Item 68: Governor Proposes To Slash Medicaid Reimbursements, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.49 (1995:Dec. 15)
  - Item 69: President Clinton Vetoes Republican Balanced Budget Bill: Introduces Alternative Medicare and Medicaid Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.48 (1995:Dec. 8)
  - Item 70: SHRPC Approves Phase I Con Reform: Takes No Action On Other Regulatory Reforms, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.47 (1995:Dec. 1)
  - Item 71: Pew Report Predicts Surpluses in Health Professions, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 72: HCFA To Make Changes in Survey Process, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 73: President Clinton Vetoes Republican Balanced Budget Bill: Introduces Alternative Medicare and Medicaid Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Continuing Care Connection, v.2:no.25 (1995:Dec. 13)
  - Item 74: Certificate of Need Intake Log, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: January 1, 1996.
  - Item 75: Certificate of Need Outcome Log, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 76: Faded Glory: Will Nursing Ever Be The Same?, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Kevin Lumsdon
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, December 5, 1995.
  - Item 77: Currents, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, December 18, 1995
  - Item 78: Hospitals Turn Attention to Assisted Living, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 79: 1995: A Record Year For Hospital Deals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 80: Poll: For-Profits and Not-For-Profits Both Have Advantages, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 81: Medical Groups in NJ Merge, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 82: For the Record, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 83: Medicare Margins Climb Through Cost Cutting, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 84: Cordtz Elected New SEIU Chief, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 85: WellPoint, HIS Pull the Plug on Merger, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- RN Division News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: RN Division News., 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: 1199 League of Registered Nurses
    Notes: Summer, 1995.
- Contract Bulletin, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: RN Division News., 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: Spring, 1996.
- 1998 Calendar, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Contract Bulletin., 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: 1199/144 Division
    Notes: no.2. A New Day Dawns for 144.
  - Item 2: Contract Bulletin., 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.2. A New Day Dawns for 144. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Contract Bulletin., 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.2. A New Day Dawns for 144. Copy 3.
- George Pataki, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: 1998 Calendar., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: 1199 National Health and Human Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO.
  - Item 2: 1998 Calendar., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 1998 Calendar., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Copy 3.
- Know the Facts About Bioterrorism, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: George Pataki., 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: 1199 SEIU.
    Language: English;Spanish.
- We Won!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Know the Facts About Bioterrorism., 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Know the Facts About Bioterrorism., 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Know the Facts About Bioterrorism., 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Your Benefits Summary Plan Description, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: We Won!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: 2002 Contract Victory Bulletin from 1199 SEIU
  - Item 2: We Did It!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: Greater New York Health Care Facilities Association Workers Achieve Drean of Contract Parity with 1199 SEIU